Now we welcome VL Ambala Ma'am.
Thank you very much ma'am for
giving us your valuable time.
Thank you so much Harsh.  Good morning to all the
viewers and you.   Yes.
And meanwhile, many of our viewers
like Sampat Sharma ji are saying Jai Shri Ram
and many more are saying Good Morning.
So a very good morning to everyone.
May this day be full of fun for you.
Cut very well.  Ambala Ma'am, I
want to hear from you.  Now tell me one thing about the market,
first of all I will tell you because we
understand things one by one.
Ma'am, the level
around 22182 was the level from where the market made
a tremendous comeback.  There was a good surge.
So tell me once that if we
see where the bottom
is seen forming at the level around 22180.  What should we assume
that the bottom has been formed?  We will not retest that level now.
Ah, I will not retest before Rs 25,500.  There will
come a time when we will actually
close at 25, right now we are 243 200 24 250 right round figure 24230, so I think once we reach
around 25500, you can keep a little plus or minus,
keep that much provision, but there
is that much probability that after that if things go
wrong then a new low can be formed,
probability it is linked with further
intensification of this, if this word intensifies
with war.  If the war is
being intensified then this bottom will come.
Otherwise consider it as a short bottom.  This is what it means.
You can take this for granted
because everything else in the market
is pricey.  Everything is discounted.   The
market is currently afraid of only one thing,
which will be a new event that will come if this
situation converts into a world war.
Otherwise no, it will not come.
Let's see, Ma'am has given a solution to one thing here
that brother Anales and Antil, this can happen
only if the conditions of world war arise.
Otherwise, in a way, the
levels here are less likely to be tested.
Tell me 25500 means ma'am the price
is almost above 200 DMA i.e. the price is 25165 which will
go above 200 DMA, it has to go above it
once.  And
if everything comes in place positively, if
everything becomes positive, see
in my view it is all about sentiment,
market is not looking what good is going to happen,
what worst is coming, market only
wants that something positive is
visible here, this escalation means this
phase of talks that is going on, this is a positive thing,
means the hit which could have happened today, it got
passed on and it is always said, this is
valid everywhere that time brings a solution for everything.
So if you're getting the time,
That Means Something might be it.  There's a
hope of Ray Ray of hope sorry.  So there is a ray of hope
in the market and that is an important
trigger point.  Apart from this, weak
earnings, growth in selective sectors,
huge dent in some.  We have already talked about all this
that fiscal deficit will increase,
trade deficit will also increase, margins of companies will
increase or decrease, inflation will increase,
currencies like going to melt ahead.  Bond
yields bring us back, all these things are in
place.  Everyone knows that this will happen because
what has already happened has an impact.  He has
already taken the price in.  The only thing which is
left is that this war should
proceed slowly, the market has no problem with it.
Some meaning, but if it intensifies and
reaches nuclear level then only there is a
concern or if countries like Russia or China
or India get involved in it.
I have already specifically mentioned the names of three countries
today.  Actually, I was
avoiding it but
if there is direct involvement of India, China and Russia then we can see something worse
in the
market which is also only up to Rs 20,000.   This can happen only if there are
no more verses than this.
Otherwise, assume that
this investment should be yours up to
70%. Save 30% just so that you can
either pyramid the profit in a rising market
or if it falls to 20,000 somewhere, then
average it there.  That's it, you should get
invested and on
Monday we were connected last time, right
ji,
and from there till now,
whatever targets were discussed for Nifty and Bank Nifty during Monday, were
for the upside only
and both have been hit, 56000
was talked about for Bank Nifty and for Nifty it was
said that it will come at least around 24300 200,
just that is
fine, so here ma'am has
explained the situation very well and see,
if you take the data of the last war and
see, even in the 10 wars that have happened, if
you look here as per our markets, then
six to seven times
we have lost maximum 8 to 9% only,
not more than that.  Ma'am,
let us talk about the back side, brother, now the
situation at the bottom has been created.  These
levels will be retested only when something
unexpected and ultimately something big happens.
But now, the situation that you mentioned about 25500, till
when will it be visible, ma'am?
Ah, not this week.  This week, that is,
this week, I have considered this week closed.
Meaning today is Thursday, tomorrow is Friday,
not in this week.  In the next week, that is,
in this monthly closing, I should see that in this monthly
closing, I am expecting the April series to be
around 25500, not the absolute number, but
around 25500. It may go
up by 100 points, it may go down by 100 points or even
150 points, but I am expecting
that this April series is going to touch the
price of around 2500 and this is possible, that is,
you just see that whatever is happening, it should be slowing
down gradually, whatever talks are going on regarding these war conditions,
but
you know, because gradually you should notice one thing,
no doubt everyone's dependence on crude is
very high, but countries, economies,
policy makers and whatever you want to call it,
corporates are being ready that
people are making a solution to this gradually, so that
means, with the focus on renewable energy, we are
not going into details, but people are
gradually finding a solution to this, that is  If
people are getting it made by emphasizing it through policies then preparations are being made.
You should understand that even if things go bad, then there is
talk of creating a cushion to be absorbed,
that cushion in the background is being
created, so it is like it is going to be a relief to the people, this
is what about the
market, but yes there is no need to be so scared
because if you keep on being scared then nothing will be achieved, this is
the market, it is a business, if you take risk then you will make
money,
absolutely ma'am and we should
also learn this thing from mutual funds, the way
they invested money in small cap in the month of March
and invested money here in a controlled manner.
So that thing looks like a lot of things.
And meanwhile,
more than 1100 viewers are connected with us.
Many thanks to all the viewers
here who join us early in the morning and
give their time.  Ma'am, a
viewer, yes ma'am, please
I want to share two stocks with you.
It's time allow.  So as soon as the market
opens, I think that if I
forget later then it will be left behind or it will be
late.  So one is IRB.  There was discussion yesterday also
regarding this, however, IRB
is still in the buying range today.
We can buy it in the range of 21 and 22
for investment.  Right?  And the possible
stop loss is that for now we are
keeping a stop loss of ₹19.5 here.  And as soon as it
crosses above 23 in intraday,
bring the stop loss to 20.  But 20 is
not your target.  Your target is ₹24.  The
first target is ₹24.  The second target is ₹25.5 and the
third target is ₹28.  And I am telling you about the
target till May.  So
a good upside movement can be made in IRB at low
risk.  Then is a fact.
Which second fact did you tell me, ma'am?
Fact Fertilizer.
Good fertilizer.  Ok.
Fact Efficacy Fact.
Ok.
Ok.  So the fact is currently running near 866.
Anyways if you are getting opportunity
in the range of 840 to 870 it is
fine.  So by considering the buying range here, the
first target will probably be 950.  The
second target will
be 1330.  And my third target suggestion is to
wait for around 10150.  And this
is also a favourable risk reward.  Because the
risk you are taking here right now is Rs 740.
And as soon as 950 is gone you either
book it.  If you want a short term one
day trade, but if you are
doing short term trade, that is, properly
looking for swing training trade short term trade opportunity, then you can do training at
800 and wait for 900 and 1150.
Ok?  So
sorry 1000 and 1150
okay?  That means the first pick
of ma'am is irrb irrb Infra, so the
levels mentioned by ma'am here are 21 to 22
for buying and a stop loss of 20 is being placed.   The
levels of 24, 25, 28 can be seen.  It may be seen
going up to ₹8.
You will have to wait till the month of May.
Apart from that, the fact is that
Fertilizer and Chemicals Travan Core,
here the prices ranging from 950 to 1050 can be
seen here.  So
ma'am, we say that whenever you come, you bring good news
for the investors in the form
of two stocks, like always, like every time.
So this is a very good thing here.
Apart from this, I will take a question from many more viewers,
ma'am.  Then I
start discussing stock specific with you that there are a lot of
stocks here.  Let us take the question of Deepak ji or
once again Ramchandra Sethi ji
here.  Let's take both of these,
ma'am.  Deepak ji's house is on top of Indus Tower.   They are
asking whether I should exit or
book the loss.  Ramchandra Sethi ji is saying
that the buying done by him in Brain B Solution is at the
price of Rs 225.
Please suggest a little about the stop loss and what will be the target.
Not 280 or 300 ma'am, the price of brainless solution is 200-225.  The
brain beast solution that
he bought,
yes first cry ma'am.  So right now let's
go to 245, the close is above at 247
and this is the same range where the recommendation was given to
break the piece AUI, so they have
held it, it's fine, there is no problem, right now
you can wait for the target of 280 and 345,
now from here you must understand like this,
280 is like, it may take you a week or two
weeks, but 345 is something that you got to hold
for like another two to three months, it may
come sooner, the probability is the
same, but you have to have a provision for that because what I am
telling you is that I am saying it will go up by 40% more than the
current price, so be
prepared for that, if you have to hold for two-three months, then
you can hold, the
rest will come soon, you can say that much,
and one ma'am is Indus Tower,
yes, Indus Tower, for how much have they bought,
they have given information, ma'am they are saying that should I just
hold Indus Tower or exit,
I am in loss  Hmm
ok I think Indus Tower is coming to 390,
390 400, it closed at 420 20 yesterday
so it can come in that range.  Now,
depending on your buying, you have to decide whether it is a swing
trade or an investment.
And when it reaches 390 or 400, it's
bye for me.  I will
look for buying opportunities there.  It
Will Be On My Radar.  It is not that if I get 300 or 400 then
I will immediately get 390 or 400.  There will be a
view of buying initiate immediately.  No we are going to
observe whether the movement is going to continue from here to the upside
or further downside.
So we're going to assess it again at
close to 390 400, but that's absolutely getting
there.
Ok?  So, there is absolute probability that
many reports have come that
due to high capital expenditure, there may be
some impact on earnings pay and free cash flow.
So, ma'am has told many things here,
reflecting them according to the feelings also.
Now let us move ahead.
Here we talk about the results
because a lot will depend on the results.
Tejas Network is a Tata company which is also moving ahead in the market.
Look at its results coming, if we look at it on a consolidated basis year after year, then first of all you have the
net profit in front of you.   A
huge decline has been seen here.  You
look at the net profit.  Earlier the
company was in loss of around Rs 71 crore.  Now it has directly incurred a
loss of Rs 211 crore.  So this is a big
number which clearly shows the loss.  If we
talk about the revenue front, the revenue here has been seen decreasing by 82%
year on year.  If
you look around, earlier it was ₹197 crores, from there it has become ₹333
crores.  Talking about EBITDA, it has
come into negative here.  So all these
things are clearly showing reflection.
And the stock has been consistently beaten up in the recent past.
Ma'am how
should Tejas Network be viewed?  What would
be your advice?
Ok.  One is an alarming condition.  In the last one
year, Q&Q has increased by about 1% (less than 1%
but up to 1%) i.e. 0.98% and
retail participation has increased by about 7.5% in one year.   So I
appreciate you all that
you believe in your trades and you hold on and
move on.  But it has been falling since last one year.
So there is no need to work anyway
because you must have understood what I mean.
In one year it has seen a decline of 47%
on the price charts as well.
Despite that, people have said in a year, that is, I have
said quarterly because the
position has changed by 1% in the last quarter and
before that it will change by 6%.  This means last
3 months before that till 9 months after that.
Why did I say that people
hold falling stocks?  Ok?  Actually, it should
not be done after stop loss.  But
this is a condition.  I am giving you one reference point
that in a stock which
showed a 47% decline in the last year,
retail participation has increased by more than 7%.
That means holdings have increased.  I mean that
means they are holding their positions.
So we are assuming that there is a lot of
retail here.  Right?  So
because data says that.  And why is that?
Because the stock has fallen in the last year,
they did not cut the position.  And once upon a
time it was like a stock of 1200 and today when
we are discussing this stock again,
not again I mean we have already discussed it but
when we discuss it today on 16th April then it is
around 450.  So the only thing to learn
here is that if you do not cut stop loss
then no one knows whether the
stock worth Rs 1000 will become Rs 10 or the stock worth Rs 10 will become Rs 1000.
So try this, you should have a
stop somewhere.  Put it somewhere.  That's all I had to
explain.  These reference points will be
understood by the rest of the people who understand.  As far as
Tejas Network is concerned,
in our most recent activities in the last month and
on AU also I think the recommendation came
in between around 400, around 350, we had bought this
stock close to 350 last
month and from there the upside
movement continued well and it is
going to further that upside movement, it is
likely that the upside movement is going to continue further.
So those who are holding it.   What
I said about retail being so big is
because those who are holding
it, whether you have been holding it for a year or
6 months or
you have picked 350 etc.,
whatever the case could be, you should now
hold it here for the
targets of 7, 570 or pardon 570, that is, there will
be a big gap between 570 and 650, the
second target is 650 and it can go up to 800.  So this is
the possibility.  These are the
possibilities that will hit me.  Now
you have to see whether your price in this stock is equal to what
you have already
bought.  If your weightage in the stock is
not very high.  There is a limited exposure.
If you are comfortable with it and your
financial advisor suggests.  So you
can also go by adding here.  This is because it is
old buying.  I understand.
This is a solution.  If you
want to look into it, then you can get a profitable
exit.  And this is why I am
suggesting it.  Because I feel that
Tejas network is still strong.
You cannot do this in every stock.  So you
can say bye to this.  And whatever position you have, it will be
your old one, if you are not too overweight in it then you
can add it and go.  For the
targets of 550 650 ground figure is 630
so that is 7 and 8.  In this way you can
catch them.  Or let's say it feels like
going from 550 to 800.
Ok?  So here clarity has come on Tejas Network from Ma'am's side
and here one of
our prime members Sudarshan Sudarshan
ji Sudha Shankar ji is saying good morning
Harsh Sir Ambala Ma'am on Cromton Griff
Ma'am
he has taken 320 shares at the level of 650.  I have taken 650 shares.
What to do at the price of 320?   Please
suggest.
One second
saying how much wait yes please take your time
ma'am.  Please take your time.  So he has
bought 650 shares at the price of Rs 320.
And how many shares did he have?  I have bought 600
50 shares.  650 shares
at Rs 320, ma'am.
All right.  So will
you be able to adjust some quantity addition?  Yes.
In my view, Crampton Grave is still
at Rs 33520, Harsh ji, it has already reached our
darpar with our members and it is an
our recommendation and the target for me from here is
a disclosure, the
target for me from here is
first of 270, then of 310 and then I am
looking at something a little bigger in it,
of 350.  So if you are convinced with this view
whose query is this, then if you want, you
can add 'S close to 240 250 range' and
today the market is most likely going to open in this range.
Today you will get
better buying in some stocks in today's market
consideration and for now you can
place your stop loss at 220. If you do
not want to add anything down the line
anyway, your exit price in six months with some profit
because it is going up to 350, then you have to make some profit as
well. So if you feel that I do
not want to increase the risk or I cannot
increase it, both the cases, then you can leave it like this, I will
come anyway. But if you feel
that you should get an early exit in three months,
then you
can add 'S' to it. It is a bullish
counter, from here it is going upwards
and the target has already been discussed, the prices are from 270 310
to 350 and the edge
off is 220.  Now the target is, as soon as our first target is reached,
we will shift it to 250.
Okay, now let us talk about SDB Financial,
its results have also come, but first let me
inform the viewers that yesterday the
stock already ran up a lot.  There was a rise of 4 to 5%
in the shares of this company.
This is a subsidiary financial company of HDFC.  Here
you have the net profit.
This shows a jump of about 41%.  Ah, if you
talk about NII here, it is 21%.  If
you talk about net interest margin,
a better situation is visible here also.  It has
increased from 0.076% to 0.082% here.
Talking about AUM, there is a jump of 11% in AUM here
which looks quite positive.  And if we
talk about total income, there too a jump of 17% is being
seen.  Ma'am, the
stock has been washed away in the recent past.   It
underperformed here but there was
a good rally in this company in yesterday's markets.
Whether the price factor is in, whether it is
seen as per the results or not, there will still be
an opportunity today.   There will be
an opportunity today too but there is a
need to have a cautious approach.  That's just
because the stock has sold out.  The stock is weak and I am
not saying anything further.  The result is bad.
I am not even saying this.  I am saying
that right now the stock has
moved around 12 to 15% in a few days, since two weeks we can
say like this, let's talk about closing April.  There has been an
upside of around 12 to 15% in April.  So, to balance the risk
reward, when the market opens today
and anyway you are getting a 1-2%
discount or let's say
to be specific that if you
get it around 640 then you can buy with 50%
exposure in which the stop loss has to be
kept small for now at 590 for chasing the
targets of like 680 and 730, this
is the minimum.  One thing that can definitely be done in this is that
as soon as possible, that is, find opportunities for profit pyramiding in it.
So as soon as you
feel that it is going above 650, you
can add further and reduce your stop loss
to 610.  So this strategy can be
used in this.  The counter is not week.
Buy on dip will work in this.
Ok?  Buy on dip will work.  Okay ma'am,
Wipro results are going to be out today ma'am.  And a
lot of the audience was waiting.
Investors were waiting to see how Wipro's
results would be.  Now we will keep an eye on those results.
But ma'am, if we look at the results of TCS, they were
not very special.
However, the decline was not as much as the street was expecting.
Well, I won the deal here too.
If we look at this, which is around 12 billion, the
business that was seen growing due to AI
also came to around 2.3 billion.
Whereas in the previous quarter it was around $1.8
billion.  This means that the
company is moving ahead in AI in terms of its implementation.
But
how are you looking at Wipro?  What equations are being
formed here, ma'am?   You should say
goodbye to Wipro and sit down.  That
is what the price is saying.  If you try
buying, there is risk everywhere.  Right?  And
if you get the same risk and reward
in the large cap industry then there is nothing like that.
If you are going to take the same risk in small cap or mid
cap or
in emerging industry, then that
risk is a little higher probability wise.
But in a stable company in a
stable industry from a stable
brand.  So all these things
coming together in one year is positive.  So having said this,
this is explained only because
today when you assume that
you are taking buy in Wipro in the range of 200 to 210.
We probably had the same conversation on Monday and we are in the same range, even today the target has
not come.  So if you take this range as a
buying consideration and you are
buying just 80%, 80% that means what you have
decided for a stock, if you are feeling scared
then buy at 80% for the stock which you have decided,
remaining in the range of 200 to 210, complete your quantity
either above 225 or
if it comes a little bit to 190 or 95 then
complete it there because your stop loss
as of now is 175.  Please listen carefully.
Your current stop loss is 175.
But your target expectation should not be less
than at 240, meaning it has to reach 240, this is the
target, so even at 240,
if your profit is pyramiding after reaching 225, then you will be, then also
you will be in a good profit and
by chance, if
sometimes, for any reason, if you get a little bit till 195
and there you are trying to improve the price, the
average price is 205,
then also your risk record will be good.
So Wipro can be considered for a minimum target of Rs 240 and a
maximum target of like Rs 2670.
Good
stock.  The time is also right.  Decide the exposure as per your convenience.  You
can take a lot of risks.  Meaning there is risk in every recommendation.
Understand this.  But if you feel that you have to
manage a little wisely.  Invest 80% and
leave the rest for profit pyramiding
or little bit averaging.  Butt will do.   I can
say this much.
Ok?  Will work.  We have got clarity from Ma'am
regarding Wipro because
today is its results and we will keep a close eye on
it, we will tell you what kind
of results have come here Ma'am, there is another company
ICIC LBD, see its results coming
today, the stock will be seen reacting
on the basis of the results, if you look here
in quarter 4, if we talk about profit then
a decent jump of 7% is seen, here it
increased from Rs 510 crore to around Rs 547 crore, if we
talk about net premium, there
is a jump of around 10% in net premium also.
Here, if you talk about gross written
premium, there is a jump of around 17% here also.
Apart from this, ma'am, there are two-three
more things.  The gross direct
premium income here has increased by 18%.  This
means that you should understand that the
growth of the industry here is 10% and its growth is
18%.  That means you have beaten
here and beaten by a good margin.
What is the second thing here, ma'am?
Another thing that investors should clearly see and understand is the balance sheet.   The
solvency ratio here
is above 2.67x.  Whereas the regulatory requirement is
around 1.50x, here
around 1.50x and this is
actually around 2.67x.  That means clearly the
balance sheet here is strong.
Ma'am, how should I read and understand the results
and should I include them in my portfolio
or not?   Should be
taken off and with all this.
So this is called the value investment.   Even
when you're better than the sector, your
numbers are good, you're doing better from the back,
and your margins are your edge.
Your margins are good.  Despite that,
if you are cheaper than the sector, that's something called I
love, yes it is okay, if you
invest money here then it does not sink very easily.
Chances of drowning are everywhere.  But
when you are putting your money in true cases then
you have a little higher chances of
rewards.  And the same combination is
currently being made in ICICI GI.  Now
what should you do in the past today?  First,
understand that this 10 has only risen 10% in the last few days.  The
round figure is 10% 12, however the
round figure has only gone up by 10%.  Flats
open today or even by 1850 if you
get a buying.  Like this you can take that if
you get it in the range of 1800 to 1850 then
buy it quietly.  Buy it and let it work for a few days.  Because we can trust such
performances that they will move ahead in the future.  That's what I am
talking about, right now
I think the range for buying is between Rs 1800 to Rs 1850.
You should definitely consider buying one.  I have
used the exact word.
Ask your financial advisor for the rest.
I think this is a very accurate counter.
And specifically in the insurance sector I got to
touch two points.  In this I will tell you
about this, something is changing in the market,
so for now I want to give two targets of 2100 and 2350,
which are big
targets, for which we are taking risk, for this
we are chasing the reward possibilities here at
least 25% including the first and
second targets and the
risk we are taking is only
7% here right now.  So you can get a risk reward ratio of more than 1:3
here.
How much time will it take in the end?  Not more than six
months is how long it's going to take.  So it's a
good thing.  If you want, you can take it
to your portfolio.
And yes, what I was saying is that there are some positive
points in the market, that is,
we have seen that the
deposits in banks like CASA etc. have reduced.  Right?
But the good thing is insurance premiums have
increased.  People did not take out their insurance
due to price inflation.  The number of
insurances has also increased.
People are investing their money in AUMs and new small
investments are coming into AUMs.  That means the
head count is increasing.  That shows that
gradually investing in our market in fine
financial security is
not a taboo anymore.  Or else it is
no longer a thing for adults.  This is the necessity
thing which people have understood or are understanding.
Now you can also understand that
my children or your children will
definitely have insurance
policies etc.  But you and I are also
trying.  Meaning, given our age, we are
also trying to get
insurance for our parents as well if possible.  If
possible, we should make some investment in someone's name.
These things are
happening.  This change
in the market is a good thing for our market
and this is why,
despite all this happening, we have not fallen much.
Okay, so Clarity Ma'am has given this very well.
Ma'am, I would like a small answer and
then we will wind up our show.  Riya
ji owns IDFC First Bank.  He has
purchased at the price of Rs 68.  He has ₹557 shares.
Want to know what to do.
How much is their buying?
Ma'am for ₹68.
All right.  So see you don't have any other option
instead to hold rather than to hold it.  You just
hold on and don't look at it again and again.  All I
can say is that if you
watch it again and again, you will get panicky.
Panic means you will feel scared.  Hold it comfortably.  In
six to seven months, when your overall market
reaches new highs, your stock is heading
towards 9095.  So you should leave it.
So now there is no need to track again and again.  It has already been
corrected quite well.
And I think there is
not much more to fall than this.  If there is anything left, it is very percentage
wide limited.  So just avoid all this
panic because if you see it you will
not be able to control yourself.  That's what I'm just
trying to make you understand.  Going from 90 to 95.
Have some patience.  A year or six months
may come soon but hold on.   Don't
look again and again.  That's what I am
suggesting.
Okay ma'am.  So, there is a lot of advice from your side
here, especially on the two IRBs, on
Infra and
also on the Fertilizer and Chemicals Shravan Core, that advice has come out
here, the pic given by Ma'am here and in it the
targets and levels have also been mentioned.  If
you want, you
can rewind and watch it as a viewer.  Ma'am recommends shopping here.
Okay ma'am thank you so much and
ma'am please share the disclaimer also.
Yes sir, yes thank you.  Even today, I do not have any
investment stocks in my personal portfolio, which we have recommended.
Members may have them in the equity channel
or in small case portfolios.
Stock recommendations on different media may have been given in the past
as common stocks remain.  So there's
one more thing I'd like to stop you from doing.
One of our viewers is JM
Baberujis over.  Because his question has been
repeated many times here.  So it is in loss of 9%.
Their buying is approximately at ₹168 and they are
asking what should be done?
GM Bru, I remember I had recommended three days ago that if the
target is not reached and the
stop loss is also not reached then hold it
and rest yes,
I have given the stop loss and target and till
now neither of them has been hit.  So hold it with that
further disclosure again that I do
not have any of the stocks in my portfolio that I have recommended to you guys here.
Trading and investment are subject to
market risk, work accordingly.
A SEBI license or registration
certificate by SEBI by NSM will be the
property of There is no way of guarantee.  And
past performance does not
guarantee future profits, nor does it
give any indication.  It's not a reference to
future performance.  So all that, the
biggest thing before leaving is
that risk management is the key and
money cannot be made without taking risks.  So this is
like your river and if you have to cross it then you will have to
learn to manage it.
Thank you so much.
Yes, learn to love with risk.
An advice is being given by ma'am.  Thank
you so much ma'am.  Thank you very much for
joining us.  Investment in the securities market
is subject to market risks.